Yes, what can I do for you?
My friend is in homestay...
and she really enjoys it...
so I'd like to join a family as well.
Okay,
so let me get some details.
What's your name?
My name is Keiko Yuichini.
Could you spell your family name for me?
It's...
Yuichini,
that's Y-U-I-C-H-I-N-I.
And your first name?
It's Keiko.
K-E-I-K-O.
That's Keiko Yuichini...
okay...and you're female.
And your nationality?
I'm Japanese.
Right and could I see your passport, please?
Here it is...
Okay...
your passport number is JO 6337...
And you're how old?
I'm twenty-eight years old.
Now, you live at one of the colleges...
which one?
Willow College, umm...
Room 21C
Right, 21C Willow College,
and how long are you planning on staying with homestay?
About four months...
longer if I like it...
And what course are you enrolled in?
Well, I've enrolled for twenty weeks in the...
um...
Advanced English Studies because I need help with my writing...
and I'm nearly at the end of my first five-week course.
Okay...
Do you have any preference for a family with children or without children?
I prefer...
I mean I like young children,
but I'd like to be with older people...
you know...
adults...
someone around my age.
Okay,
and what about pets?
I am a veterinarian so that's fine...the more the better.
All right, now what about you?
Are you a vegetarian or do you have any special food requirements?
No, I am not a vegetarian...
but I don't eat a lot of meat...
I really like seafood.
And what are your hobbies?
I like reading and going to the movies.
Do you play any sports?
Yes, I joined the handball team,
but I didn't like that..,
so I stopped playing.
Now I play tennis on the weekend with my friends...
All right, let's see, name, age, now the location.
Are you familiar with the public transport system?
No...
I'm not really because I have been living on campus...
I've been to the city a few times on the bus,
but they are always late.
What about the trains?
I like catching the train...they are much faster...
Now, let me go check on the computer and see who I've got...
Listen, leave it with me...
I'll check my records and I'll give you details this afternoon.
Thank you for helping me...
It's a pleasure.
Bye.